在AsyncTask的文件中，我们可以
In the documentation for Async Task, we can
滑到谈论关于保护方法的部分
scroll down to the section that talks about
这里我们将看到在
protected methods. Here we see that different methods
用户界面线程与后台线程中被提及
are called on the UI thread versus on the
的各种方法。它还包含了调用这些被提及的方法的信息
background thread. It also contains information on what
相对于
order these methods are called in. Relative to the
doInbackground方法。例如，方法onPreExecute 在
doInBackground method. For example, onPreExecute gets called on
用户界面线程中比方法doInBackground先被提到。所以现在有了这些消息
the UI thread before doInBackground. So with that information
我们就能填写我们的测试答案了。在
now, we can populate the answers to our quiz. As
我们注意她之前，方法onPreExecute 发生在主线程中，并且
we mentioned before, onPreExecute happens on the main thread. And
在这你可以做任何调整工作。然后方法doInBackground发生在
here you can do any setup work. Then doInBackground happens
后台线程中。当这个运行时，你就可以
on the background thread. While this is running, you can actually
任性地使用publishProgress了，然后
call publishProgress as many times as you want, so that
你就可以传递信息给用户界面了。再然后
you can pass information to the UI. So that it
就能更新并且告诉用户一个
can update and then tell the user that a certain
关于工作已经完成了多少的准确百分率。每一次被通知的时候，
percentage of the work is done. Each time this is called,.
就会触发onProgressUpdate还有一些信息。然后，
It triggers onProgressUpdate with some information. Then,
你就可以看到一个等待中的进度条
you can show a loading indicator in
在你的用户界面里，并且显示着已经完成10%，完成50%，完成100%。并且所有这些
your UI that says something's 10% done, 50% done, 100% done. And all this
都是发生在主线程中的。然后，一旦所有都在后台线程中完成了，
happens on the main thread. And then, once all of this is complete in
那么就会通知在主线程中的onPostExecute
the background thread, then it calls onPostExecute
以及结果。
with the results on the main thread.